Guide to the Collective: Unconscious Archive MSS.225
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Video
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous
    - "Toys in Playland", 1997; ID: 225.0183 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0183)
    - "Traces: Three Takes on the Generational Separation of Family", undated; ID: 225.0184 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0184)
    - "Twilight of the Dark Master", undated; ID: 225.0185 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0185)
    - "UFOs Are Real, a Brandon Chase film", 1993; ID: 225.0186 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0186)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0187 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0187)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0188 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0188)
    - "LG" (?; crossed out text: "up tree with chainsaw"), 1997; ID: 225.0189 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0189)
    - Untitled (flower stamp), undated; ID: 225.0190 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0190)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0191 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0191)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0192 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0192)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0193 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0193)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0194 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0194)
    - Untitled, (starred), undated; ID: 225.0195 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0195)
    - untitled, undated; ID: 225.0196 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0196)
      Currently unavailable until duplications occurs.
    - Untitled, container has crossed out text: "Opera and Ghost of Canterbury", undated; ID: 225.0197 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0197)
    - "The Violent Years (Mamie Van Doren hosts Teenage Theater)", 1985; ID: 225.0198 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0198)
    - "White Disabled Talent (excerpts)", undated; ID: 225.0199 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0199)
    - "Julian Whatley, Director of Photography, Commercial/MV Reel, Series IX; Wildchild Editorial", undated; ID: 225.0200 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0200)
    - "CVR - ABC News; Wolf's tape", March 22, 2000; undated; ID: 225.0201 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0201)
    - "Vervolg: Eternal Jew (Wolf NYC)", undated; ID: 225.0202 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0202)
    - "Nazi UFOs & Illuminati Conspiracy; The Eternal Jew; nazi propaganda (Wolf NYC #1)", undated; ID: 225.0203 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0203)
    - "Love Poem Cinema" (Korean video), 2000; ID: 225.0204 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0204)
    - Korean video, undated; ID: 225.0205 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0205)
    - Foreign Language Video, undated; ID: 225.0206 (Box 15, Media ID: 225.0206)
- Series VI: Audio
  Series VI: Audio consists of original and miscellaneous audio recordings of Collective: Unconscious and other groups. Subseries B, Originals, contains recordings of Collective: Unconscious productions, most documenting anti-slams and Faceboy. Subseries C, Miscellaneous, includes commercial albums, mixed tapes, and unidentified materials.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Audio materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - "AntiSlam", February 10, 2004; ID: 225.0207 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0207)
      Original format: audiocassette
    - "AntiSlam", December 2, 2004; ID: 225.0208 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0208)
    - "AntiSlam pt 1", February 24, 2004; ID: 225.0209 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0209)
    - "AntiSlam pt 2", February 24, 2004; ID: 225.0210 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0210)
    - "AntiSlam", March 4, 2004; ID: 225.0211 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0211)
      Currently unavaiable until duplication occurs.
    - "AntiSlam (1)", March 3, 2004; ID: 225.0212 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0212)
    - "AntiSlam (2)", March 17, 2004; ID: 225.0213 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0213)
    - "AntiSlam (3)", March 24, 2004; ID: 225.0214 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0214)
    - "AntiSlam", March 24, 2004; ID: 225.0215 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0215)
    - "AntiSlam (1)", March 24, 2004; ID: 225.0216 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0216)
    - "AntiSlam (1)", April 14, 2004; ID: 225.0217 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0217)
    - "AntiSlam", April 14, 2004; ID: 225.0218 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0218)
    - "AntiSlam (1)", April 21, 2004; ID: 225.0219 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0219)
    - "AntiSlam (2)" (side a: "Texas"), April 21, 2004; ID: 225.0220 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0220)
    - "AntiSlam", May 5, 2004; ID: 225.0221 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0221)
    - "AntiSlam", July 4, 2004; ID: 225.0222 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0222)
    - "Faceboy", February 22, 2004; ID: 225.0223 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0223)
    - "Faceboy", February 29, 2004; ID: 225.0224 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0224)
    - "Faceboy (#2)", February 29, 2004; ID: 225.0225 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0225)
      Format: audiocassette
    - "Faceboy (1)", March 7, 2004; ID: 225.0226 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0226)
    - "Faceboy (2)", March 7, 2004; ID: 225.0227 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0227)
    - "Faceboy (1)", March 21, 2004; ID: 225.0228 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0228)
    - "Faceboy (2)", March 21, 2004; ID: 225.0229 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0229)
    - "Faceboy (3) (LG - andere kent)", March 21, 2004; ID: 225.0230 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0230)
    - "Face[boy] (1)", April 4, 2004; ID: 225.0231 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0231)
    - "Faceboy (2)", April 4, 2004; ID: 225.0232 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0232)
    - "Face[boy] (1)", April 25, 2004; ID: 225.0233 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0233)
    - "Face[boy] (2)", April 25, 2004; ID: 225.0234 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0234)
    - "Faceboy" [sibe b: "LG"], May 9, 2004; ID: 225.0235 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0235)
    - "For Wolf", undated; ID: 225.0236 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0236)
    - "Fringe Festival, Rev. Billy Show", August 21, 1999; ID: 225. (Box 16, Media ID: 225.)
    - "Kople NYC (#305) [illegible annotations]", undated; ID: 225.0238 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0238)
    - "Match Game", February 28; ID: 225.0239 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0239)
    - "AntiSlam, Rev. Jen (1)", January 6, 1999; ID: 225.0240 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0240)
    - "DM Post 1; NYC Kople (152); side a: Genetica/man [illegible annotations]; side b: Boycot/Israel", undated; ID: 225.0245 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0245)
    - "DM Post 3; NYC Kople", undated; ID: 225.0246 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0246)
    - "Kople NYC (nazi propaganda recordings)", undated; ID: 225.0255 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0255)
    - "Whap spankking; Mee nr NY", undated; ID: 225.0256 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0256)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous
    Access copies for Subseries C may not be available. Please contact a Fales Archivist.
    - "Biet Het Is Prop! (vol. 2)", undated; ID: 225.0241 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0241)
      Original format: CD
    - "Bodibalance Warm-Up For Dancers, Carol Fonda", undated; ID: 225.0242 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0242)
    - "Spoken Words, by Nicolet Brouwn", 1996-2000; ID: 225.0243 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0243)
    - "Alex Chilton, 'Cliches' (Ardent Prod.)", 1994; ID: 225.0244 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0244)
    - "Eat Static, 'Science of the Gods' (Mammoth Records)", 1997; ID: 225.0247 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0247)
    - "F. Labrel", undated; ID: 225.0248 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0248)
    - "Fantasizing in the backseat of a minivan about having kids in a montecarlo", undated; ID: 225.0249 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0249)
      Format: CD
    - "Hanna-Barbera Cartoon Sound FX (Rhino)", 1994; ID: 225.0250 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0250)
    - "Hedwig and the Angry Inch, The Long Grift (Atlantic)", 1999; ID: 225.0251 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0251)
    - "Tom Leher, 'That Was The Year That Was' (Reprise)", undated; ID: 225.0252 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0252)
    - "The M Word", 2002; ID: 225.0253 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0253)
    - "The M Word", undated; ID: 225.0254 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0254)
      Original format: 3" CD
    - "Musigyny 'The CD of the Movie of the Book of the Play'", 2000; ID: 225.0257 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0257)
    - "Narb 'High in the Mountain' (Orchard St. NY)", April 8, 2003; ID: 225.0258 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0258)
    - "The Best of the National Lampoon Radio Hour Vol. 3 (Rhino)", 1996; ID: 225.0259 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0259)
    - "'St. Reverend Jen' and Other Theme Songs by Rob Paravonian", undated; ID: 225.0260 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0260)
    - "Poison Idea/SSD/Bad Brains...", undated; ID: 225.0261 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0261)
    - "Pope John Paul II: The Pope of the Rosary (Radio Vaticana)", 1995; ID: 225.0262 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0262)
    - (illegible scribble), undated; ID: 225.0263 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0263)
    - "Puccini 'La Boheme' (RCA)", 1964; ID: 225.0264 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0264)
    - "Ramones, It's Alive", undated; ID: 225.0265 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0265)
    - "Rant", undated; ID: 225.0226 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0226)
    - "Sanctity, 'In the Name of the Mother' demo tracks", 2003; ID: 225.0267 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0267)
    - "Smetana Ma Vlast, My Country, Rafael Kubelik (London Records)", 1988; ID: 225.0268 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0268)
    - "Jim Stiene, 'Enema Verite' (Warped Records)", 2003; ID: 225.0269 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0269)
    - "John Todd: Prophecy for the 80s (Kople 133)", undated; ID: 225.0270 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0270)
    - "Mad About Vivaldi", 1985; ID: 225.0271 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0271)
    - "MP3s voor Wolf", undated; ID: 225.0272 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0272)
    - "From Wolf [illegible annotations]", undated; ID: 225.0273 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0273)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0274 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0274)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0275 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0275)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0276 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0276)
    - untitled, undated; ID: 225.0277 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0277)
      Original format: microcassette
    - Foreign Language Recordings, undated; ID: 225.0278 (Box 16, Media ID: 225.0278)
- Series VII: Computer Discs
  Series VII: Computer Disks contains several 3.5" diskettes and one Zip disk.
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - "Bass", undated; ID: 225.3.0001 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0001)
    Format: 3.5" diskette
  - "Akai Os Backup" [crossed out text: "Manifestations, December 97, #1 of 2 backup"], undated; ID: 225.3.0002 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0002)
  - "Spart 2, disk 3 of 3", undated; ID: 225.3.0003 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0003)
  - "Spart 2, disk 2 of 3; Mikon 2", undated; ID: 225.3.0004 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0004)
  - "Spart 2, disk 1 of 3; Mikon 1", undated; ID: 225.3.0005 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0005)
  - "Manifestations January '98, disk 3 of 3", 1998; ID: 225.3.0006 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0006)
  - "Manifestations, January '98, disk 2 of 3", 1998; ID: 225.3.0007 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0007)
  - "Manifestations, December '97, #2 of 2", 1997; ID: 225.3.0008 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0008)
  - "Manifestations, December '97, #1 of 2", 1997; ID: 225.3.0009 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0009)
  - "Manifestations, December '97, #2 of 2", 1997; ID: 225.3.0010 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0010)
  - "Manifestations, January 98, disk 1 of 3", 1998; ID: 225.3.0011 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0011)
  - "Hanna Barbera #1", undated; ID: 225.3.0012 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0012)
  - "Hanna Barbera #2", undated; ID: 225.3.0013 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0013)
  - "Hanna Barbera #3", undated; ID: 225.3.0014 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0014)
  - "Hanna Barbera #4", undated; ID: 225.3.0015 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0015)
  - "Hanna Barbera #5", undated; ID: 225.3.0016 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0016)
    ID: 225.3.0016
  - "Hanna Barbera #6", undated; ID: 225.3.0017 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0017)
  - "Hanna Barbera #7", undated; ID: 225.3.0018 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0018)
  - "Man EP 5, disk 1, bomber and machine gun (L)", undated; ID: 225.3.0019 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0019)
  - "Man EP 5, Disk 5 (No 4), explosion", undated; ID: 225.3.0020 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0020)
  - "Manifestations, Fifth Column #1", undated; ID: 225.3.0021 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0021)
  - "Manifestations, 5th Column #2", undated; ID: 225.3.0022 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0022)
  - "Manifestations, 5th Column #3", undated; ID: 225.3.0023 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0023)
  - "Penis Plunge, Stab, Doorbell, Door", undated; ID: 225.3.0024 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0024)
  - "Bad Things", undated; ID: 225.3.0025 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0025)
  - "Akai 5900, K-muse, LA - Sustained Sounds", undated; ID: 225.3.0026 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0026)
  - "Akai 5900, glass ball, choir, voice-string", undated; ID: 225.3.0027 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0027)
  - "Synth bass", undated; ID: 225.3.0028 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0028)
  - "Man EP 5, disk 7, gas hiss, stake plunge, punch 1, punch 2, braincry", undated; ID: 225.3.0029 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0029)
  - "Man EP 5, disk 9, bootmarch, air raid", undated; ID: 225.3.0030 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0030)
  - "Man EP 5, disk 10, gun, punch, sword", undated; ID: 225.3.0031 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0031)
  - "Falling Women and Rocks", undated; ID: 225.3.0032 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0032)
  - [untitled], undated; ID: 225.3.0033 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0033)
  - [untitled], undated; ID: 225.3.0034 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0034)
  - [untitled], undated; ID: 225.3.0035 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0035)
  - [untitled], undated; ID: 225.3.0036 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0036)
  - "Win 98 startup; blank", undated; ID: 225.3.0037 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0037)
  - "Playpractice pictures, 7/99", 1999; ID: 225.3.0038 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0038)
  - "Resumes", undated; ID: 225.3.0039 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0039)
  - "Collective Backup", undated; ID: 225.3.0040 (Box 17, Media ID: 225.3.0040)
    Format: Zip disk
- Oversize
  Oversize includes oversized material from: Series I, Subseries A, B; Series III; and Series IV.
  - Oversize Series I: Subseries A
    - Monthly Calendar, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 279 Church St. blueprint, undated (Folder 24 Right)
  - Oversize Series I: Subseries B
    - Alliance of Resident Theatres [post-9/11?] poster, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Misc. production posters, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Signed posters - "The Sayanas"; "The Caedmon Kids", undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Annie Sprinkle posters, ISWFACE (International Sex Worker Foundation for Art, Culture and Education), 2002 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - "Deadly Departures", Christine Negroni book poster, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Videotaped performance notice, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - The Porno Jim Show poster, undated (Folder 25 Right)
    - N-Ho-Tep production posters, undated (Folder 26)
    - Fabric C:U sign [used in Monster Parade, Mermaid Parade], undated (Folder 27)
  - Oversize Series III
    - Misc. photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Oversize Series IV
    - Misc. photocopies - patterns/artwork, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Paintings/backdrops (Box 19)